Robert "Rocky" Salerno

Email: rrsalerno21@gmail.com | Cell Phone: 831.521.0205

Portfolio: rrsalerno21.github.io LinkedIn: linkedIn: linkedIn: londout.com/in/rockysalerno GitHub: github.com/rrsalerno21.

SUMMARY OF QUALIFICATIONS

Technical and collaborative full stack developer with two years of experience working in fast paced SaaS environments. Currently enrolled in UC San Diego's Coding Program and a leading contributor amongst the cohort. Seeking to secure a full time web developer position and further improve technical skills.

TECHNOLOGIES

- HTML5
- CSS3/SASS
- JavaScript/jQuery
- Bootstrap
- Vue.js
- React

- Node
- **Express**
- MongoDB
- MySQL
- Command Line
- Git

EXPERIENCE

Front End Developer (Contract - Part-Time)

July 2020 – Present

- SoldNest, Campbell, CA
 - Technologies used: HTML5, CSS3, SASS, Javascript/Typescript, Vue.js, Zenhub, Git
 - Optimize web application and marketing website's functionality, scalability, and presentation
 - Build new landing pages that follow and uphold company direction, formatting, and responsive design
 - Follow developer workflow and branching strategy through Github and Zenhub

Strategic Account Manager/Customer Success Manager

October 2019 - March 2020

Raken Inc., Carlsbad, CA

- Operated as Product/Development/Customer Success team liaison to develop sales tools and SOP's
- Wrote and executed manual front-end quality assurance tests for bugs in production and development
- Functioned as team lead and onboarding trainer during transitional period between managers

Associate Website Production Specialist

July 2018 – September 2019

AppFolio Inc., Goleta, CA

- Utilized HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, and web design skills to create over 100 websites
- Ran manual QA tests on websites to ensure bug free performance
- Contributed to the successful transition and rollout of a new internal website platform

EDUCATION

University of California, San Diego Extension - Coding Program, Part Time

Currently enrolled, expected graduation in September 2020

University of California, Santa Barbara

Bachelor of Arts in Mathematics and Minor in Science and Mathematics Education Graduated June 11, 2016

To see all of my previous work experience, please visit my LinkedIn at www.linkedin.com/in/rockysalerno